fmces.com 2008-09-21

# Future Management Consulting Ltd-FMC--HOME--Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy Statement disclosed the privacy practices of Future Manage-ment Consulting Ltd. (“FMC”), in respect of the personal information provided whether in person, by mail, email or fax, or through our website. This has been is a fundamental base in building interdependence with our candidates and clients.

FMC is an executive search firm which may obtain information sensitive. The statement demonstrates our commitment to you. 

The main principles of our code of conduct on this statement are:

1. We will not sell or share the information to other companies or institutions.

2. We use personal information only with permission for the purpose of executive search. 

\---Individuals whose personal information has been processed by our firm  
     have the right to know the following information: 

 ◆ Whether or not information has been processed 

 ◆ The purpose of the processing

 ◆ The recipients to whom information has been disclosed 

3. We protect and control the processing of collection, use and disclosure, in case of any unauthorized disclosure.

4. We store and retain personal information in our database in strictly confidential.

5. We assure that our clients acknowledge they will adhere to the same standard   
    of this statement. 

FMC reserves the right to update this Privacy Policy if necessary. We also welcome your comments on the privacy practices. You can send your comments or enquiry to [ashley_liao@fmces.com](mailto:ashley_liao@fmces.com)
